눈뜨면 안돼
Come on, no peeking.
Our eyes are closed, and we're
crossing the street. Very good.
눈감고 길을 건넌다
현명한 짓이지
자, 이제 봐!
Okay. Open up!
What do you want to show us?
뭘 보라는 거야
이건 야시시한 밴이잖아!
Because all I can see
is this bitchen van!
It's for our catering business.
출장요리사업에 쓸 거야
I think I know that girl.
어디서 본 듯한 여자인데
We won't keep it this way, though.
- 이대로 쓸 건 아냐
- 그래?
이 칼을 바게트로 바꿀 거거든
We'll replace the sword
with a baguette.
Oh, my God, I think I lost
my virginity in that van.
내가 이 밴 안에서
처녀 딱지를 뗐었나?
근데 문제는 이거야
Also, we don't know
what to do with this.
Oh yeah, I definitely know her.
그래, 확실히 아는 여자야
The One Where
They're Going To Party!
Remember that guy from cooking school
that put cilantro in everything?
아무 데나 조미료를 넣던
그 남자애 혹시 기억나니?
Sure, Cilantro Larry!
그래, 조미료 래리
I'm filling in for him as
food critic for the Chelsea Reporter.
걔 대신 '첼시 리포터'에
음식비평을 기고하게 됐어
와우! 영향력 있는 인물이
될 기회네? 몇 명한데는...
What an amazing opportunity
to influence...
...dozens of people!
우리 사업은 어떡하고
What about our catering business?
일주일에 하루면 돼
It's just one night a week.
너희들 공짜 저녁 얻어먹을
건수도 많이 생길 걸?
Plus, I get to take you out
for free dinners.
Well, in that case....
그렇다면... 얼쑤!
That was me, hopping on board.
나도 끼워달란 뜻이야
Hey, guys. Hey, Ross!
얘들아, 로스
하나 물어보자
Quick question for you.
Are you ready to party?
파티에 갈 준비됐냐?
I could maybe go out
for a couple of beers.
글쎄, 맥주 한 잔
하는 거면 모를까...
There's this thing about bees
on the Discovery Channel.
디스커버리 채널에서
땅벌 다큐 나온다는데
I don't think you heard me.
Are you ready...
아니, 내 말 잘 들어
파티에 갈 준비 됐냐니까
...to party?
No.
설마!
Gandalf?
Gandalf is coming to town?
갠돌프가 오는 거야?
I have nothing to do, so tomorrow
we are partying with Gandalf, dude!
캐시도 부모님 댁에 가고
내일은 갠돌프의 파티야, 임마!
Dude, we are so going to party!
임마, 바로 그 파티구나
Wow, okay. Dude alert!
알겠다, 임마들아
Who is this guy?
그 친구가 누군데?
Mike "Gandalf" Ganderson.
Only the funnest guy in the world.
마이크 갠돌프 갠더슨
배꼽 빠지게 하는 녀석이야
I'll call to get off work tomorrow.
난 내일 월차 낸다
I'll call after you!
다음은 나야!
This will be so cool!
We never party anymore.
오싹하다, 야!
이런 건수가 생기다니
Were you smoking something
in the back of our van?
우리 밴에 들어가서
뭐 말아 피운 거 아냐?
"We never have fun anymore"?
You have fun with me.
그게 무슨 소리야
나랑 놀아도 재미있잖아
Remember those strippers?
And you paid me $50 to eat that book?
스트립쇼 구경에다, 50달러
걸고 내가 책 먹어치운 건?
너도 맘에 들 거야
갠돌프는 파티의 마법사거든
You are going to love this guy.
Gandalf is the party wizard.
Why do you call him "Gandalf"?
왜 갠돌프인데?
Gandalf the Wizard.
마법사 갠돌프
Didn't you read
Lord of the Rings in high school?
너 고등학교 때
'반지의 제왕' 안 읽었냐?
No, I had sex in high school.
여자애들이랑
새롱거리느라 바빴다
Joanna? I was wondering if
I could ask you something.
저기요, 궁금한 게 있는데
There's an opening for
a buyer in Junior Miss
여성복 구매부에
자리가 났다고 해서
나 더러 좌천을 당하라고?
-That'd be a step down for me.
-Actually, I meant for me.
아니, 제 얘기예요
The hiring committee
is meeting people all day and....
오늘 면접이 있대요
나로선 안타깝지만 언제까지
내 조수 노릇만 할 순 없지
I guess you can't stay
my assistant forever.
소피도 그렇지만
이유는 좀 다르지
Neither can you, Sophie,
but for different reasons.
I'm so glad you don't have a problem.
If you did, I wouldn't apply.
만약 반대하셨다면 저로선
꿈에도 생각지 못할 일이에요
In that case
- 그렇게 된 거라면...
- 문제가 없다니 저도 기뻐요
That's why I'm glad
there's no problem.
I'm on the hiring committee,
so there'll be one friendly face.
나도 그 위원회 소속이니까
분위기가 낯설진 않을 거야
That's great!
그거 잘됐네요
Junior Miss is where I started.
나도 그 부서에서 시작했어
I slept with the ugliest guy
to get that job.
엄청난 흉물단지와
동침한 대가였지
-Really?
-No.
진짜예요?
아니
Yeah.
맞아
I mean, no.
아냐, 그럴 리가 있나
With your qualifications, you won't
need to sleep with some guy.
자기 정도 능력이면
남자랑 잘 필요는 없겠지
내겐 성의표시만 해줘
Although I might need
some convincing.
농담이야
Kidding!
God, I feel wild today!
오늘 좀 된다 얘
멀미가 다 나네
토해도 되냐?
Man, I am so excited,
I may vomit.
Will you calm down?
He's just a human guy.
웬 호들갑이야
걔가 신이라도 돼?
You don't understand.
He's amazing.
네가 잘 모르니까
그런 소리가 나오지
You never know what'll happen.
예측불허라니까, 맥주를
한잔하다 정신 차려보면
You go out for beer
and end up on a boat to Nova Scotia.
캐나다 노바스코샤의
낚싯배에 앉아있다니까
-Really?
-It's beautiful country up there.
- 진짜?
- 경치 한번 절묘하더라
Hey. Okay.
좋았어
I got my passport, fresh socks,
and a snakebite kit.
여권도 준비했고, 새 양말
독사 응급처치 구급약
It won't be exactly like last time.
누가 저번이랑 똑같댔냐?
I'll see you guys.
그럼 이따 보자
I have an audition,
but I'll meet you.
오디션 끝나고 만나자
12시쯤 어디 있을래?
Where will you be around noon?
Somewhere maybe along the equator?
적도 근처를 헤매고 있을 걸?
알았다
Hello.
여보세요?
It's Gandalf!
갠돌프야!
So are you in town?
도착했어?
Oh, well....
Maybe next time, then.
다음을 기약해야지 뭐
What happened?
왜 그래?
He can't come.
He's stuck in Chicago.
시카고에서 발이 묵였대
환장하겠네!
시카고는 복 터졌다
Oh, man!
Chicago's so lucky.
엠병땜병할 캐나다 돈
Stupid, useless...
...Canadian money!
You have a very impressive resume,
Miss Greene.
아주 좋습니다, 서류철 방법을
고안한 건 특히 인상적이에요
I especially like what I see about
implementing a new filing system.
Thank you.
감사합니다
Filing system? Those colored labels
you put on all the folders?
서류철이라면... 폴더마다
알록달록한 딱지 붙인 거?
It did brighten up
the filing cabinets.
캐비닛이 화사해지긴 했죠
그게 다는 아니랍니다
They did more than that.
I notice you've been entrusted with
a lot of important responsibilities.
성실한 근무태도로
상사의 신임이 두텁군요
네, 부장님께 많이
배우고 있습니다
Joanna really has been
an incredible mentor to me.
아침마다 제게
베이글을 사다 주는데
Rachel has been incredible
at getting my bagels.
She gets it right almost every time.
한 치의 실수도 없답니다
Of course, I have more
responsibilities than that.
물론 다른 업무도 있죠
그럼, 커피 배달도 있으니까
두 가지를 동시에 나른답니다
Of course!
There's the coffee too.
Rachel can carry two things at once.
That's very good.
네, 감동이군요
Now a big part of this job is...
이 업무는 디자이너들과 각별한
친분을 유지하는 게 핵심인데
...cultivating personal relationships,
especially with designers.
-Yes, l
-She shouldn't have any problem.
- 네, 그건 저도...
- 그건 염려하실 거 없어요
Her only problem might be getting
too friendly, you know?
너무 가까운 게 오히려 문제죠
I love working with designers.
전 디자이너들과 함께
일하는 게 좋아요
함께 일하든 밑에서 일하든
그게 그거 아니겠어?
With them. Under them.
What's the difference?
My first review is out.
얘, 내 글이 실렸어
The Chelsea Reporter.
진짜 첼시 리포터잖아
이거 덮으면 되게 따뜻한데
These used to keep me so warm.
뒷장을 봐
Look, I'm on the back page.
여기다
"Would I go back to Allesandro's?
Sure, I'd get two meals.
알렉산드로에 다시 가면
꼭 2인분을 주문할 것이다
One for me, and one for the guy
pointing the gun to my head."
나와 내 머리에 총을
겨누고 있는 사람을 위해
You really laid into this place.
찐하게 두들겨 맞았네?
They don't pay me a penny
a word to make friends.
나 놀러 다니라고 한 단어에
1페니씩 주겠어?
I found a guy who'd fix up
the van for catering.
나가야겠다
- 누가 밴을 개조해준대
- 같이 갈까?
You want me to go?
아니, 괜찮아
물침대 진짜 필요 없어?
It's okay. Are we sure
we don't want the waterbed?
Because it would be silly to take it out
if we're just gonna put it back in again.
어차피 다시 달 건데
떼어내면 뭐해!
이미 끝난 얘기잖아
Haven't we made this decision?
Yeah, all right.
그랬구나
- 다녀와
- 그래
-Who is it?
-It's Allesandro, from Allesandro's.
누구세요?
알렉산드로 식당의
알렉산드로외다
- 엄마야
- 할 얘기가 있소이다
-Oh, my God.
-I want to talk to you about your review.
어머, 이를 어째...
전화로 하세요
Call me on the phone.
그냥 끊으시게?
What? So you can hang up on me?
I'll never let you up,
so just go away.
문은 못 열어줘요
그냥 가세요
-Just give me a chance to
-Do you need to get in?
- 일단 내 얘기나 들어보고...
- 문 열어드려요? 됐어요
안돼! 피비!
No, Phoebe!
Hey, Monica!
안녕, 모니카
I want a retraction.
Our food is not "inedible swill."
정정하쇼, 우리 음식이
어딜 봐서 돼지 먹이요
I couldn't eat it.
난 못 먹겠어요
My five friends couldn't eat it,
and one of them eats books.
내 친구들도 다 그렇대요
책을 먹는 애도 있는데
Our service isn't
"grossly incompetent."
서비스는 개판 5분전이다?
The waiter carried
the breadsticks in his pants.
웨이터가 바지춤에서
막대빵을 꺼내줬어요
Well, you said that we accept
the Discover Card...
그리고 우리가 언제 디스커버
카드를 받았나, 이 사람아!
...which we do not!
All right, that I'll retract.
좋아요, 그건 정정하겠지만
But I stand by my review.
I know food, and that wasn't it.
그 음식은 뭐라고 해도
좋게 봐줄 수가 없어요
Your marinara sauce tastes
like tomato juice.
마리나라 소스는
토마토 주스 같으니까
보드카랑 셀러리를
곁들여 내시죠
You should serve it
with vodka and celery.
I'm proud of that sauce.
It's delicious.
보쇼, 그 소스는
우리 업소의 자랑이야
You own an ltalian restaurant,
and you think that tastes good?
기가 막혀서, 이태리 레스토랑
주인 입맛이 고작 그 정도예요?
Where are you from?
고향이 어디죠?
Lebanon.
레바논
Hand me those tomatoes.
그 토마토를 줘보세요
제가 한 수 보여드리죠
I'll show you
what it should taste like.
어서요
손봐줄 글쟁이가 또
있으니까 빨리 끝내쇼
How long will this take?
I got another critic to yell at.
Joanna, I want to talk
about that interview.
부장님? 아까 그
면접 건 말인데요
I thought it went very well.
잘된 것 같은데
No, it didn't. That's what
I want to talk to you about.
그게 전혀 아니라서
드리는 말씀이에요
Now just to brief you...
요점만 보고 드리죠
...I may cry.
제가 우는 건...
But they are not
tears of sadness or of anger...
슬픔이나 분노의 뜻이 아니라
...but just of us having
this discussion.
이런 내 신세가
너무 처량해서
Please, don't make a scene.
사람들 눈을 생각해
There's nobody here.
누가 본다고
소피, 들어와
Sophie, get in here.
See? You're making
Sophie uncomfortable.
봤어?
소피가 불편해하잖아
No, she's not.
불편한 거 없는데요
Congratulations. You crossed the line
into completely useless. Get out.
역시나 무능한 요원의 표본을
제시해줬어요, 퇴장하시죠
Do you want me to quit?
제가 그만둘까요?
뭐? 왜 그런 생각을 해
What makes you think that?
Those things you said
in the interview...
아까 그 말씀이 진심이라면
전 자격이 없는 직원이에요
...if you believe them,
I must not be a good assistant.
알았어요
You know what?
I am just going to pack up my desk...
책상 정리하죠
...and I will be gone
by the end of the day.
오늘 내로 그만둘래요
There's no use staying
till the end of the day.
뭉개고 있어봤자
달라질 것도 없네요
Wait, wait.
잠깐 기다려, 가슴 아픈
머핀은 도로 집어넣고
You can put
your sad little muffin back.
If you must know the truth, I didn't
want to lose a good assistant.
사실대로 말하면 유능한
직원을 놓치기 싫었어
What?
네?
That's why I said those things
about your flirting and drinking.
남자 밝히는 주정뱅이라고
한 것도 다 그 때문이야
My drinking?
주정뱅이?
나간 다음에 한 얘기군
I must have said that
after you left.
Said what, exactly?
정확히 뭐라고 하셨죠?
You enjoy the occasional drink...
술을 가끔 입에 대면
코가 삐뚤어진다고
...-ing binge.
Oh, my God!
That is it. I'm leaving!
맙소사, 더는 못 참아요
정말 상종 못할 사람이군요
You are just a horrible person!
왜 이래, 성질 참
황당하게 급하네
Wait, wait.
If you're going to get
all sensitive about it.
I don't want to lose you.
자길 잃고 싶진 않아
What if I create a position for you?
자리를 하나 마련해볼게
이 부서의 구매담당은 어때
I'll make you assistant buyer
in this department.
Say more things like that.
거기가 끝이에요?
Your own office and a raise,
effective tomorrow.
개인사무실에 봉급인상
당장 내일부터
-I need an expense account.
-Done!
- 개인경비계정
- 좋아!
-And an assistant.
-Sophie!
- 비서는?
- 소피, 들어와
Hey, I thought you'd be
out partying with Gandol-...
너희들 여기서 뭐해
'걘돌머리'는 어떡하고
...-dorf.
It's Gandalf, and he's not coming.
갠돌프야
못 온대
You've been sitting here all day?
- 종일 이러고 있었냐?
- 아니, 수표책 결산했다
I balanced my checkbook.
And I gave first names
to all the foosball players.
난 축구선수들 이름 붙여줬어
I can't believe he didn't come.
인생사 참 허탈하다
So what? We can still go out
and party ourselves.
뭐 어때, 우리끼리 놀면 되지
갠돌프가 있으면
밤을 꼴딱 새우는데
With Gandalf, we'd be out all night.
낯선 사람이 다 뭐야
하염없이 놀아버려
We'd meet total strangers
and hang out with them.
We could do that.
우리라고 못해?
There was other stuff too.
어찌 그게 다겠냐
We'll do it all and better!
까짓 거 우리가 더 잘해
After tonight, Gandalf will want
to party with us, dude!
갠돌프가 우리한테
붙을 거야, 아자!
- 뭐 파티가 별거냐?
- 그렇지, 출동!
It's not like we don't
know how to party!
All right! Let's go.
Maybe we could end up
on a boat again?
마무리는 보트로 하나?
- 예에!
- 옳다구나!
All right!
야, 보트는 언제 탔냐?
When were we on a boat?
Remember that cold morning
with those dogs licking your face?
살 떨리게 춥던 날, 개들이
얼굴을 핥아서 잠에서 깼지?
- 그래
- 실은 물개 떼였어
Those were seals, man.
How would this suit
look on an assistant buyer
얘, 이거 어때
구매담당한테 어울릴까?
The owner of Allesandro's
came to yell at me.
알렉산드로 주인이
따지러 왔었는데
But I made him sauce, and he
offered me the job as head chef!
내 소스 맛을 보더니
주방장을 맡아 달래
엄마야! 오면서 준비한 말을
못하게 됐지만 너무 잘됐다
You just ruined the thing
I was practicing, but I'm so happy!
Can you believe it?
I get to run my own kitchen!
- 드디어 내 주방이 생겼어
- 고생 많았다, 얘
Oh, you've waited so long.
Pheebs! Quick question for you.
- 피비, 하나 물어보자
- 그래
How would this suit look...
이게 블루밍데일의
구매담당한테 어울려?
...on an assistant buyer
at Bloomingdale's?
그 여자 피부색 문제지 뭐...
It would totally depend
on her coloring and....
You got the job!
너 승진했구나!
You got the job?
Why didn't you tell me?
승진했니?
왜 얘기 안 했어
근사하지 않아?
It'll be so great!
I'll help decide what we sell.
판매품목을 내가 결정하고
벽으로 둘러싸인 개인사무실
I'll have an office
with walls and everything.
I'm going to have walls!
벽이 생겼다니까
오늘 경사가 겹치네?
나도 일 따왔어, 결혼 피로연
Is this the day of good news or what?
I got us a job.
The wedding reception.
I kind of need to
talk to you about that.
피비, 그 얘기 좀 하자
I think it's time for me to take
a step back from the catering.
난 이쯤해서 출장요리
그만둬야 할까 봐
But we've only had one job.
겨우 한 번 하고?
But now we have this second one,
and it feels like it's snowballing.
그건 아는데, 이런 식으로
나가면 눈덩이처럼 불어나
What are you saying?
무슨 소리야?
I got offered the head chef job
at Allesandro's.
알렉산드로에 주방장
자리가 났어
뭐?
It's okay, because
you don't really need me.
우리 사업에 내가 꼭
필요한 건 아니잖아
You're the cook!
요리사는 너야!
Without you, it's just me
driving up to people's houses...
나 혼자 빈 접시 내밀면서
돈 내놓으라고 떼 쓰냐?
...with empty trays,
asking for money.
All right. But I'll pay you back
all the money you invested.
그건 그렇지만....
네가 투자한 돈은 다 갚을게
그 밴도 너 가져
-And you can keep the van!
-For what?
어디다 쓰게
I can't believe this!
너무 한다
I got to get out of here.
- 나 갈 거야
- 피비, 기다려
Phoebe, wait a minute.
I'm an assistant buyer!
난 구매담당이다!
We'll get coffee, get energized,
then head back out.
커피로 원기 회복하고
다시 나가는 거야
-Yeah, all right.
-Okay.
- 그래
- 좋지
So we're having fun, right?
재미있었지?
마법사가 별거냐?
We don't need that wizard guy.
We hit some clubs,
talk to some strangers...
클럽에도 들르고
낯선 사람도 만나고
...then go down to the docks
and see about that boat thing.
이제 선창에 나가서
보트 건만 해결하면 돼
I'm kind of beat.
난 좀 지친다
Actually...
솔직히... 나도
...me too.
Are you serious?
- 진심이냐?
- 그럼
Thank God! I'm exhausted.
실은 나도 맛 갔어
You guys want coffees?
커피 줄까?
I don't want to be up too late,
so I'll have a decaf.
일찍 자야 되니까
카페인 없는 걸루다
그래요, 나도
Yeah, me too.
Actually, could I get
some hot water with lemon?
레몬 동동 띄워서
따끈한 물 한 잔
목소리까지 갔나 보다
웬 동네가 그리 시끄럽냐
I strained my voice screaming in there.
Does it have to be so loud?
I can't hear a word.
My ears are ringing so bad.
아직도 귀가 윙윙거린다
I was glad I had
that extra pair of socks.
다행히 양말을 가져가서
장갑 대용으로 썼잖아
I used them as mittens.
마지막 집은 돼지우리더라
I didn't want to touch a thing
in that last place.
How sad are we?
이게 웬 청승이냐?
Yeah, I know.
누가 아니래
You know what?
We're not sad.
청승이라니, 우린 이제
21살 청춘이 아냐
We're just not 21 anymore.
You know?
난 스물아홉이라고
I'm 29 years old, damn it!
I want to sit in a
comfortable chair, watch TV...
편안하게 TV 보다가 일찍
잠자리에 드는 게 더 좋아
...and go to sleep
at a reasonable hour.
그럼
분위기 조용한 데 가야
친구랑 대화를 나누지
I like to hang out in a quiet place
where I can talk to my friends.
그렇지!
집에서 케니 지 걸어놓고
목욕하면 얼마나 죽이는데
And so what if I like to go home,
put on Kenny G and take a bath?
We're 29.
We're not women.
우린 29살이지
여자가 아냐
There you are.
여기 있었구나
I'm glad you decided to hear me out.
얘기 들어준다니 너무 고맙다
Okay, I'm hearing.
들어나 보자
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
생각 많이 했어
I came up with a bunch of businesses
that you can do with your van.
밴 갖고 할 수 있는 일이 많아
보자...
You could be
a flower delivery person.
- 꽃 배달 서비스도 좋고
- 뭐?
-What?
-Or a bakery delivery person?
아니면 빵 배달은?
Pizza?
피자?
모니카!
이 분야에 업종이 꽤 다양한데
넌 배달업이 별로인 것 같다
I got a whole bunch
of stuff in this area.
But I get the feeling
you don't want to deliver.
-No.
-Okay.
그래
좋아
I guess if you
don't want to deliver...
배달 일이 별로라면
택배사업도 싫겠지?
...you probably don't want
to pick up stuff either.
No.
그럼
You know what?
아무래도 안 되겠다
출장요리 다시 하자
Let's do the catering business.
-Really? Are you sure?
-Yeah, I made a commitment to you.
- 진심이야?
- 너랑 약속했잖아
It'd be fun.
- 재미있을 거야
- 당연하지!
It will be fun!
그럼 피로연 준비하자
Let's plan the wedding reception.
좋았어, 히히!
You really wanted me
to do something with this van.
사업구상 엄청 많이 했구나
You know what?
I want you to take the chef job.
아니다, 넌 주방장 일 맡아라
-Really?
-Yeah.
- 진짜?
- 그래
That's what you really want.
넌 그게 하고 싶잖아
I don't want to be the reason
you're unhappy. I'd be unhappy.
너 불행해지는 건 싫어
그럼 내가 불행해지고
그건 더더욱 싫어
And I really don't want to be
the reason I'm unhappy.
Thank you.
고맙다
Besides, it might be kind of fun
to form the new A-Team.
A 특공대를 다시
조직해도 신나겠다
Hi, Mrs. Lynch.
안녕하세요?
부장님 나오셨어요?
Is Joanna in already?
Oh, my goodness!
You haven't heard.
- 저런, 아직 못 들었군요
- 못 듣다뇨?
-Heard what?
-Joanna...
조애너는 간밤에
세상을 떴어요
...passed away last night.
맙소사, 어쩌다가
Oh, my God! How?
She was leaving work,
and she was hit by a cab.
퇴근하다 택시에 치였대요
- 세상에! 이런 일이 있다니
- 그러게요
Oh, my God!
I cannot believe it!
I know.
맙소사
Oh, God.
저런...
아뿔싸!
I didn't realize
that you were so close.
그렇게 가까운 사이였나요?
Yes. So close!
네, 무척이나!
물론 우리 모두에게
힘든 시간인 건 알지만
I know that this is an emotional
and difficult time for all of us.
But by any chance, did Joanna...
혹시 부장님이 서류 같은 거
보낸 적 없나요? 사고 전에?
...send any paperwork
your way before...
-...it happened?
-No, nothing.
그런 거 없었는데
Imagine, if she'd just stepped off
that curb a few seconds later.
조금만 기다렸다 건너지
뭐가 그리 급하다고
네, 그렇게 허망하게
가실 줄이야
Yes, just a few seconds
and she'd still be with us.
구매담당 얘기는?
Nothing about an assistant buyer?
I'm sorry. I have to go.
미안해요, 가볼게요
Good morning!
안녕?
소피, 부장님 소식
못 들었구나
I guess you didn't
hear about Joanna.
I sure did!
물론 들었지
I'm excited about having
Monica on board with us.
모니카를 영입하게 된 건
더할 나위 없이 기쁘지만
Although I do feel bad
about having fired Chef Emilio.
해고된 에밀리오 주방장을
생각하면 목이 메이는군요
It is like losing
a member of the family.
가족과 생이별한 기분이에요
Of course, that literally
is the case for several of you.
물론 여러분 중 몇몇은
사실이 그렇겠지만
토니, 카를로스, 마리
Tony, Carlos, Marie...
...please tell your father
how much we're going to miss him.
아버님께 많이 그리울 거라고
꼭 전해주세요
I know Monica has a lot
of great ideas for this place.
모니카한테 참신한
아이디어가 많아요
Well, you all read the review.
다들 기사를 봤겠지만
So without much further ado...
여기서 각설하고 우리의
새 주방장을 소개합니다
...I present to you
our new head chef.
I just want to say that
with a pinch of excitement...
간단히 할게요
최소한의 열정과 성의
협동심으로 무장한다면
...a dash of hard work
and a dollop of cooperation...
...we can have the recipe....
본 업소의 앞날은...
Are you going to kill me?
죽일 건 아니죠?